sheridanmentoring.com 2008-08-28

# Sheridan Options Mentoring

### Sheridan Options Mentoring Privacy Policy

Feb 11, 2007

At Sheridan Options Mentoring we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Sheridan Options Mentoring or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post separate privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information. 

Sheridan Options Mentoring servers are in the United States and adheres to the US safe harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the [U.S. Department of Commerce's safe harbor program](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/index.html). 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Sheridan Options Mentoring, Attention: Privacy Matters, 1539 Della Drive, Hoffmann Estates, IL 60169 USA. 

### What information is collected?

**Personal Information:**  
We require personal contact information and property information from our members. The required information is used to effectively and accurately create, maintain, and display Sheridan Options Mentoring's services. The required information varies with each site of the Sheridan Options Mentoring network depending on the industry and its relevant data. 

**Cookies:**  
Some sites in the Sheridan Options Mentoring network utilize cookies in order to provide members and merchants with a more personalized experience by remembering who you are when you revisit the site. Cookies also track visitor activity and traffic patterns among the sites so that we can identify users' interests and behavior. With this information, we can improve existing user services and develop new products appropriate for our audience. 

**Third-Party Ad Companies:**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, CLICK HERE back to the top 

### How is the information collected?

Members are requested to submit personal information to verify their membership to use Sheridan Options Mentoring services. Users unwilling to pass personal information online will not be allowed to use Sheridan Options Mentoring web-based services. 

### How information will be used? 

**Resale and Disclosure of Information**  
Sheridan Options Mentoring reserves the right to sell or disclose some personal information collected on our site to third parties. We may provide third parties with non-exclusive, limited use of Sheridan Options Mentoring's collected information in order for the third party to promote and market the third party's service. Any right of the third party to distribute, transfer, transmit, or re-sell Sheridan Options Mentoring's information is prohibited. 

**Privacy of Sheridan Options Mentoring E-mail Lists**  
We collect and record personal information in order to maintain e-mail lists. We utilize the e-mails to keep members informed of the site services, site performance, promotions, and offer information regarding industry related services and products. back to the top 

### User choices in receiving and distribution of information 

**Sheridan Options Mentoring E-mail Lists**  
Sheridan Options Mentoring maintains e-mail lists to periodically send information about special promotions and advertising tips to current e-mail list members. E-mail list members who do not wish to receive the mailer can send a request via e-mail to be removed from the mailing list or follow the directions at the end of each emailed message. Sheridan Options Mentoring reserves the right to include third party advertisements that provide additional services to members in the e-mails we may send. 

**Third Party Distribution**  
Members may receive information directly from third parties that have related services. Members that do not wish to receive the third party information can opt-out by contacting Sheridan Options Mentoring. Third parties receive only the needed personal information in order to effectively target members' needs and interests. Third parties have non-exclusive, limited use of the information provided by Sheridan Options Mentoring. Any right of the third party to distribute, transfer, transmit, or re-sell Sheridan Options Mentoring's information is prohibited. 

### Data Security 

**Personal Information**  
To protect the member's account information, Sheridan Options Mentoring assigns each member with either a unique user name. These unique user names are disclosed to the user via e-mail immediately upon the members application being accept into the Sheridan Options Mentoring web site. Only members have the ability to modify their personal information and update or delete their personal information as needed. 

**Credit Card Transactions**  
Sheridan Options Mentoring uses GeoTrust Premium SSL Certificates and secure servers to transmit all online credit card transactions in an encrypted format. 

### Data Quality and Access

Members may access their information 24 hours a day using their designated login. Members may modify or delete their information as needed. 

### Changes to this policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. 

### Questions

If you have further questions that were not addressed in the above privacy policy, please contact us at: 

Sheridan Options Mentoring  
Attention: Privacy Matters  
1539 Della Drive  
Hoffman Estates, IL 60169  
USA
